No, no, no. You're after me.
- 50 crowns is holding.
- No. Must be 35 crowns.
Only two this coupon apply if you
receive the bouquet.
My dear, I have a bouquet required.
Half of 70 is 35.
50 crowns a bouquet. 70 the price of
the bouquet of two crowns.
This is very unreasonable.
It's so crazy. I'm going to complain
this to consumer rights.
- Is your supervisor here?
- No, she took a lunch break.
Lunch break? It would be better once
he learns to do math.
The same thing for two different
prices? It's insanity.
Just so you know...
familiarization with two bouquets
ever!
I'll miss you.
A man by the name of OVE
Translator: Achilles
None of them are useless.
- Dog stop peeing in my yard.
- Don't listen to the old man.
Anders! Did you see what he did? The
prince tried to kill.
- What did you do with the dog?
- She's not a dog.
Looks like a boat with eyes double.
- They don't allow dogs here.
- Don't confuse the police.
Can you say something to him, Anders?
You're chairman of the board of
directors.
I said now.  No, I really mean
it.
Good Morning.
Is everything all right? You're not
in the mood to chat?
- Ove! For a minute, can you come?
- Office.
Now you're going to get promoted, huh?
- Is everything all right?  Yes.
- How long you're working here, you
Ove?
- 43 years.
- Come on.  Damn.
- It is the duty of the father over
you?  Yes.
We will offer you a very good.
More than 59'undasin. May have other
plans for her life.
A 43-year than in the same place?
Well...
- You want to fire me.
- Wouldn't phrase it that way.
But you're close.
- We want to offer you a program.
- Some kind of formal training course.
A little step further.
- Digital technology sticks
everywhere.
I have a proposition for you.
Wouldn't it be easier if I go out?
It's nice. It's what we do.
Wait, Ove. We have a farewell gift.
A garden shovel.
If you must direct you there if you
are moving to phone services.
- There is no phone.
- Are you kidding me?
Take it slow. You come.
Watch out for them. Hello, Hello!
Slow!
Stop. Stop! Stop!
- Wow.
- Ian, What?
- Go forward a bit, Patrick!
- What are you doing?
- Not very smart.
- Allowed into the car here.
- Can't read the Swedish signs?
- Are you blind? Am I driving you?
Nice to meet you, Patrick.
Mickey Mouse you say, if you're going
back...
The steering wheel if you break a
sweat, and you're looking at the
mirror.
- What's the saying?
- I don't know. Persian.
Isn't it beautiful?
No, hello!
- No, wait!
- Did I hit something?
Get down! Stop by the side of the
road!
- Don't forget... thanks. You can
drive a car.
- What is it?
- Rear camera.
Is the camera? Ian...what camera
Hello.  Hello.
Mom!
It's the rear camera! Cassette player
even more for you!
- Petter!
- Idiots.
Shit, I can't find my jacket.
- Petter! Petter!  Yes.
- Come here, Petter!
- What do you want?
PARKING IS STRICTLY PROHIBITED!
Go check!
I bought my bike. Can I get back?
- A girl's bike isn't it?
- My girlfriend.
- Where she lives?
- Number 142.
The Communists used is scrap?
- You can then come and get your own.
Anyway.
- Should I leave it in my bike?
- A strange man.
Hi, Ove. Is everything all right?
Why does everyone ask that? If not,
so what?
You're not at work. In the middle of
the day, before he got sick never.
You want something? Or life you're
gonna talk about?
Do you want to eat lunch?
Idiots!
Fucking maniacs! Allowed to drive
here!
- Did you say something?  Yes,
this is in no cars.
- So what? You have my permission.
- I'm sure there are.
- Bye. - Drive!
- Make a Def go!
There is no problem?
If a guest comes, separate parking.
That's what we decided.
They're coming from the municipality.
Home they brought the rune.
It's too cold in the House. Can you
come and take a look?
No. Use extra blankets!
Sorry I couldn't make it yesterday.
I just couldn't. Home it's turned
into a circus.
Across the new neighbors came in.
You'd be shocked to see the new
generation. They can't handle
anything.
Yanasami back is you can't even
change a tire.
You want a little something, they're
busy with lunch.
Think of. Soon we will be busy with a
country that is just lunch.
You're lucky you weren't be a part of
this.
On the street, a white car entered.
Literally freaks.
There is order in the house while you
were gone.
If we hurry, maybe we can get each
other today.
I've missed you.
Again, Ian!?
Yes? What is the problem?
- We brought rice and chicken.
- Do you sell rice?
Just a little food for help.
Food Iranian saffron. Is very good.
Parvaneh is great at cooking...
...eat in.
I pulled the trailer. I saw the note.
You're right, it was our fault.
- We thought that maybe you're hungry.
- No, I'm not hungry.
- Then we'll get there.  No,
anything in there will not be put out.
- I guess there was a ladder.
- Of course there are.
Everyone there must be a ladder
around here. There is our
Constitution.
If one were to read you'd know.
Can we borrow yours then, right?
It feels safe to be someone always at
home.
Here is their support.
Instructions for use this also.
Okay... shit!
- Bug do you have a key?
- Hexagonal key.
No, 'insect' key.
What has that got to do with the bug?
Six-pointed; hexagonal key.
Look at Google!
Ove? Can you check on the radiator?
- Please?
- The radiator water.
- Is it him?  Hello. I Parvaneh.
- This is my husband Patrick.
- Nice to meet the new neighbors.
God, it's so nice here. A paradise
for children.
Damn. No one isn't going to work now?
- Warmer or not?
- Remove?
It is not personal no one. Someone
will empty the water.
Maybe Rune before you get a stroke
from me, he should have it.
- Please Love her, stroke stroke.
- Is stroke stroke!
- Do you want to support?  Yes,
yes.
Love everyone while my husband was
chairman of the board of directors
voted rune.
Parvaneh! I mean, look. Wonders...
Import them. They was for Sonja.
- Unfortunately, Sonja a...
- shut up now! Stop!
That's enough! Get out of here, your
home!
Get out!
Heaven, huh?
Ove?
Ove? Can you come and take a look?
Yes. Should I come over?
Ove?
- What a beautiful library.
- So.
How's the book?
Here, the kitchen and the ones in the
box in the warehouse.
I'm going to make a library.
They say that the brain works
faster when it is dying.
Like the outside world was moving
in slow motion.
I've had much time to think about
enough. In fact, more about
heating.
And about my mom. It was early.
Showing people it wasn't from my
father, her sorrow.
- Thank you for coming.
- I wasn't.
Dead is dead.
One thing is for sure.
We can't repeat what we have
experienced in this life.
Let's O V E, we're going home.
My dad didn't talk much. She took
care of the house more.
And cars. She didn't talk too much
cars.
It can set you free cars.
But if you do bad they'll take away
your freedom to them.
But that night spoke.
Ove? I want to know that everything
is interconnected.
- A Saab 92.  Yes.
- What is the spark plugs?
- Allows you to move in.
Definitely.
This Ove... that's the life!
They won't never make a better car
than the Saab.
But mostly never did.
I was going to my dad's office
after school.
Hi, Dad!  Hello Ove!
He said that it was for the
best.
Get off the tracks, Ove!
- Get off the tracks, Ove!
- What do you say?
Look behind you!
The first contestant to me,
probably my dad.
I don't know why, but my mind and
my mom walked in.
You should be more careful.
Probably thought of my mother.
Thus, I had the opportunity
winding.
Here. Ove, okay. Leave your father
now.
Everyone was very nice to her
said. How polite can I be a human?
I met up with my dad's work
friends.
- Tom was one of them.
- Give it to me.
- No. I found it.
- You'll get a spanking now...
Sometimes, it does not know
whether what you're doing is
right.
- Just feels.
- You little rat.
Sometimes, the pain can be
directly related to sensation.
We have found we take. As always.
Ove?
Do whatever you want with your
wallet. Found you.
- I found on the train.  Thanks.
- Tom, Why didn't you report it?
- We're going to rat out others.
- I thought I'd get a wallet.
Yeah, I know.
But in the end it did deliver.
Honesty is the best thing Ove.
But sometimes needs a little help.
- Do you understand?  Yes, I
understand very well.
Let's go home. Jump in.
It was a day I'll finally know
true freedom.
Hi, Dad.  Hi, Ove.
- How did it go?  Yes, see for
yourself.
Is very good. Have you seen it?
That, gentlemen?
Have you seen the notes already? He
will be our new Foreman!
What? Fives and fours. Is
extraordinary.
Call the foreman! Call the foreman,
for God's sake!
Dad!
Ian, What?
This is what you are selling garbage,
huh?
You say it is a worldwide brand.
"Pulls everything!".
What did you use?
Idiot.
Even it's not possible anymore to
find a sturdy rope.
New neighbors pass by everywhere.
Saffron rice they eat.
What's wrong with meat and potatoes?
Dinner has what you need to add
incoherent!
Me for the first time you had to wait.
Hey! What are you doing?
- Prince scratched.
You throw a stone and I'll do the
puskullu the mat!
That's a chihuahua. Cat and rabies
and also plague.
Obviously, so are you. But we we
don't stone you.
Do you think you can do whatever you
want? Disgusting old man.
- I'll tell Anders.
- Well, go ahead!
But Audi already lasted that one can
understand.
Four in the front bumper, Zero One at
the wheel.
If I peed again I'll electrify my
fence!
Idiot. This goes for you too.
Go head! This is private property.
I took the hose on August 27. Now you
need it.
- Irrigation in the month of March
are you gonna?
- Did you water, and now I'm watering.
Can you look at the radiator while
you're at it?
Thanks. I think it was really sweet
that. I had dinner in the oven. Do
you want to?
Thanks, I already ate.
- I understand. I'll get the hose.
Rune? Rune?
Just so you know, everyone on the
site is doing what you want.
It will ruin the layout we had.
The hell with them. I don't care.
In fact, I'm thinking of leaving for
good.
I'm going to Sonja. I thought it
would be good to know.
Anyway, you can't do anything. You're
just sitting there and you're
watching...
Dinner's almost ready.
Thanks for the loaner. You're very
kind.
- Don't you want a little bite?
- No.
- Jimmy will eat.
- Cabbage rolls, Ove. Great.
- Rune would be very grateful.
- What hear nor understand.
Understand Rune more than people
think.
Even in your head like few even
understand.
So, now I have to go.
Drop hose!
Drop the hose is!
Hi, Ove! We're trying to get in the
window.
- Outside? Good luck!
- You're holding the ladder aren't
you?
You need to hold the ladder. Where
Are you going?
THANKS, IT WAS DELICIOUS. OVE
At least I can count on Saab.
The director is waiting for you.
It's too bad.
If you need anything, just ask.
Your grades were very good.
This is yours. It's more of my
father's salary.
Is paid in advance also.
- We can't get the money back.
The truth is what it is.
Maybe we'll find another solution.
My father's colleagues, they knew
what to do.
What will you do now that your father
is in heaven?
No, not that one. Not that!
Not that one.
Sometimes there comes a time when
you must decide.
Let's see who wants it.
Here's your wallet, you little shit.
For me it was Decision Time.
This hour is mine!
- Lindahl e, do you?  Yes.
- We've been looking for you.
- So what?
We were going to take a look to your
home.
It's a question new planning for this
area.
The new plan doesn't seem like your
home.
No Stig, we're going to be upfront.
As you can see, your house is falling
apart.
This is his first meeting with
them it was, but it wasn't the
last.
They didn't say their names, where
they came from, they told me to
just.
The men in white coats.
Always they got what they want.
- Ove? Give me some Dec.
- End was over.
I can say it wasn't so bad.
The men in white coats but they
don't like.
Hello.
Some people tells us that destiny
is the result of our own
stupidity.
Also the thing that changed my
destiny...
...I would say that is the
stupidity of people in my
neighborhood.
Is there anyone in the House? Is
there anyone in the House?
Help!
Hello? Hello?!
- A fire hose broke!
- I'm coming in!
I tried to convince the
firemen.
At that time, that man appeared again.
Turn off the water, turn the water
off. Is about to be destroyed anyway!
Do not attempt to extinguish!
In the white shirt.
How long we're on the move?
- About an hour.
- Damn!
I would if I knew it was going to
land.
So cute when you were asleep. Did you
fall asleep?
No. It's no problem.
Tickets.
Thanks.
- I don't have my ticket.
Then you buy a ticket.
I'm sorry, I don't have money.
- I have.
Here.
- I'll pay you.
- Not a problem.
I'm reading master and Margarita.
- Do you know?
- No.
The book also without a ticket I have
a cat.
Never have you read Mikhail Bulgakov?
No, nothing I haven't read the
works.
- Read the works I haven't.
I am a teacher.
I'll get off here.
Wait! You forgot that.
From then on, every morning at
7:30 I boarded the train.
But that was gone.
After three weeks, I was about to
give up now.
Hello.  Hello.
- Do you usually have in this train?
Yes.
I I'm in the army.
The Thing Is... In The Regiment.
I wanted to give the money for the
ticket.
Wouldn't it be better if you invited
to dinner?
Dinner? Of course.
Though I don't have a place where I
can cook.
The restaurant I meant to.
Of course.
- Of course, if you're going to a
restaurant.  Yes.
Okay then.
- Definitely.
Hi! Hello.
- You're fifteen minutes late.
- So what? Am I Late?
Well...
- Do you know about cars?
- Is one the car?
It might be interesting to know how
they move.
It is not as simple as it seems.
Think of a car. For example, a Saab
93.
Need a motor and an energy source.
Saab piston engine uses.
The piston, the crankshaft moves.
The best part is that it is front
wheel drive of Saab.
Therefore, the propeller shaft will
not need.
He took care of my dad's cars.
- Won't eat anything else?
- No, I ate at home.
Why did you eat at home?
You can order anything else you want.
I lied to you. I'm not in the army.
I'm cleaning up trains. Also my house
was burnt down.
I'm going now.
Thanks, it was very nice.
I'm interested in what me
asked.
"With the house" I said because
that was the only thing that came to
my mind.
Then told me some of course.
Two years later, I was a trained
engineer.
- Congratulations!  Thanks.
How beautiful it is.
Let's see what is written in Diploma.
- "Ove is blind..."
- will you marry me?
I thought if you want, we...
Speak calm and clear.
- Will you marry me?  Yes!
Yes, I'll marry you!
Yes, yes, yes!
Damn! Damn!
- What are you doing?  It's - what
are you doing that?
- You have to take me to the hospital.
- A little nose bleed?
Patrick fell down the stairs.
I knew this would happen, you idiot.
Drive yourself. I'll give you a
sewing machine come the next day.
I don't have my license.
- How old are you?
- 30.
- 30 years old and have a driver's
license do you not?  Patrick, went
by ambulance, he could die.
- I can go on the bus. Thanks!
- I use then.
Great, finally. Is this so hard?
- Where to now?
- To pick up the kids.
- It stinks.
- Mom, I can't breathe.
- Roll down the window then.  No,
you can't.
Remove the glass. Remove Windows.
- Wait!
- Can't you go faster?
Please Love, no one in the hospital
asks for a ticket.
Will last for fifteen minutes.
She's under observation. I'm
entering, meet me here, okay?
- Wait a second, what about the kids?
- They will stay with you.
Hey!
- Book.  Yes, I see.
- Book.
- He wants to read.
"Bruno every day every Tuesday, or
whatever day it started."
"Gold-Ivar, you're going to be an
engineer when you grow up,"he
shouted."
The book is boring.  Yes, I
don't like.
You must do as she tells the story,
your voice it's like talking to the
moon.
- Not a talking bear.
- Speaks to this.
"I was a machinist for a long time
already, I'm der Herr Bruno. "
Yes! Just like that, good job!
"Every Bruno he pushes the red
button. "
- "Hundreds of honey bees"... Hi
guys!
- Look, a clown!
- Beppo The Clown is here, hi!
- Do you want to see magic?
- I was reading the story to the
children.
She's reading, but I'm here now.
The five crowns do you have change? I
need crowns for number five.
Five crowns.
Thanks. It's Showtime!
Can you tell me where you live?
- Just leave it to the kids?
- I didn't leave the kids.
These losers who think himself the
police pulled me over.
Your father was carrying a security
risk.
Only five crowns I want it back!
TA-DA!
Beppo The Clown offers his thanks!
Hey, stop! Not that I gave you the
five crowns.
- Poor baby.
- I want own five crowns.
What are you an idiot?
Hey! What are you doing?
It's not my fault, the shoes were
larger. They are not funny, they are
useless.
- Ha! This is outrageous!
- Did what?
- Pay. My punishment.
- My car, though.
- Bye, Ove.  Good - bye, Ove!
Domestic 3214, and a third goes off
the rails.
Help, for God's sake!
Are you stupid? Reach out your hand!
Stretch out your right hand! Come on!
Are you stupid?
Dad!
What's wrong with you? You want to
die?
- Saved.
- It.
"Saved him" you have to say.
Idiot.
Ove!
She drew a picture for you NASA. Wait
there.
Here. NASA's I drew for you.
You're the one with color. You always
color paint.
- All the time.
- A very good idea my mind came up
with.
Teach me to drive. Patrick can't do,
and you're better.
No, I don't have time.
- I'll pay for the gas.
It's a good idea, isn't it? What was
that?
God, that poor kid!
Here.
- Open the door.
- Not in my house.
Open the door now!
God, it's freezing in here. Bring a
blanket.
- Why?
- Quick, Come on!
Hey, buddy. I was outside, I heard
screaming.
No, I know better than that. Stop.
They say fat people it produces too
much heat.
- I'll have something to keep you
dry.  No, go in the kitchen!
What the fuck is this? It's pretty
low.
- Was for Sonja. My wife.
- Where is it now?
He... He Died.
She was a very good cook. I used to
eat here all the time. Right, Ove?
I guess a little better. Him, who
will?
I can't take it. Children have
allergies.
Fuck, I forgot. Me too.
A man wasn't as easy as it is thought
to kill himself.
And now this. Before I got rid of him.
I'll be back again. I promise you,
Sonja.
Was sick like this since the
beginning. Don't think I did
something to him.
I'll see you soon.
Thought you didn't like kids.
Of course I love you, I don't know if
I would be a good father.
Ove you, you're the best dad our kids
could ever have.
I swear to God.
Idiot!
Sorry Love! Do I hit? We're
practicing with Anders.
Hi, Ove.
- Teach you this dude?
- But you wanted to help.
- We need to put on our belts.
- Right.  Will let me do.
Bye!
Be careful. Please notice that my leg!
How did that happen?
- I'll get you out the door.
- Sit your ass down.
Yesil sign Do you have? While
learning how to drive, you need to
put the rear window.
I can't watch another idiot an idiot
teach you how to drive.
Great. Thanks!
Hi, Ove. Is everything all
right?
- Read the manual to learn.
Beautiful weather for driving.
I brought you some Iranian food. I'm
as good as cooking or driving.
Sit down.
Stop. It's all red.
I'm a complete loser.
Yesil now. You can drive. Don't
forget the clutch.
God, this is stressing me out!
Run again. Turn the key.
Pull in the clutch, step on the gas.
- , I'm making too!
- Release the clutch...
I can't do it!
Enough, you bastard!
You Were you never a beginner? Can't
you see the sign?
- Calm down, little old man.
- "Little old man"!
I'm not the little old man, you
bastard!
"Big old man".
If you hit the Horn once again will
be the last thing you do. Do you
understand?
Listen to me carefully. You have two
kids...
you'll get a third soon.
You came here from Iran, war, and
other hell you ran from.
You learned a new language, you can
make a living and you were trained.
You're married to useless. You can
get the fucking car.
It's not brain surgery.
Now run it again and drive.
Idiot.
It's nice.
No, no, no! I bought it.
No, no, no. Here!
This was Sonja's favorite bakery.
We sat here at 1 p.m. every Thursday.
This is on the table.
Napoleon cake did you eat?
- How did you know?
- Today, Thursday, one o'clock.
Then what were you doing?
At two o'clock we were home.
Sonja usually read a book, we have
used Ru and to wash cars.
We have washed ourselves. The paint
would be the machines that draws.
Rune?
- You're not talking to you.
- In time we were talking.
In fact, we are very much alike.
Stop! I said stop it!
- Rune.
- Ove.
- We were working together.
- I'm going in a beeline for the
front.
- You can't drive a motorcycle here.
- Tell your friends.
We share the same principles.
In the site at the first meeting,
I was elected the chairman of the
board.
...Vice president at RU. We
thought it was the right choice.
We have friends for both of us
even we are baffled.
Then we saw little difference
between us.
- Volvo are you using?  Yes.
What Have you got?
Saab.
At first we tried to act normal
and be okay with it.
We've done.
He's a boy!
Over the years we opened.
Then, without any warning, You
bastard, you removed me from the
board of directors.
I got so angry...
I bought a Saab 9000 CS and go.
Rune on it, bought a 960
executive.
When the son grows up, suddenly
decided to move to America.
They didn't say much of anything
about it.
I was looking at a new Saab 95
and...
...I figured it was time to leave
behind the hatred.
We should talk again.
- I was thinking about.
Old disputes shouldn't be on the
shelf?
Of course. We are friends.
- It was during that period.
- Would you like to see my new car?
BMW.
I turned around and went home. Now
he had given up rune.
Volvo Drive For Life a human can?
This was his final betrayal.
Never isn't your child?
It's two hours.
Ove, I have problem in writing. Can
you help?
It is part of the driving test.
Thanks. This will be very good.
You're familiar with them already.
- Who?
- The kids, of course.
- I don't know if this is a good
idea.  - , Too. Stay in the House?
No, it is a great idea.
- Call me if anything happens.
- Bye.
I'm hungry, I'm hungry!
You're against animals testing, but
to test the kids you're not.
NASA's food he wants before bedtime.
We have to wash our own dishes. My
dad's the dishwasher, he couldn't.
Says tomorrow they will take down
from the window.
Come on, you should see my room.
What is the most important thing when
you build a house?
Water.
- And sewage.
- Definitely. An infrastructure.
- Did you build the House previously?
Yes, but this is not one of the
stones.
He said I was the best in class.
You want that?
No! Wow!
- Sepideh?  Hi, Mom.
Sleeps.
What is this?
What are you doing? You again?
With your girl's bike he says, "it is
forbidden to park the bike".
Sonja doesn't live here? I was his
student.
What I've been reading what I was
writing, but he didn't think that I
am stupid.
Then I learned everything. He was a
great guy. I'm sorry to Bother You.
- What will the bike do you?
- I'll fix it for my girlfriend.
I'll fix up, maybe my girlfriend
would be. I need to go to my other
job. -Where?
I work in a kebab restaurant. I'm
saving up for a car. A Renault.
Is it French? Did you buy a French
car?
Then the old was one of the students.
Now, as before, one more thing I need
to figure out. This situation is!
Stop! Hey!
It's nice. Stop. You can parallel
park now.
- I crashed the car.
- Not.
That's a Volvo. Wait here. I have a
job.
The bike was repaired. You can give
your girlfriend.
- Did you fix this?
- Changed the tire.
- Are you eating kebab?  No, why
would I eat you?
- What is he doing here?
- What is the black paint in your
eyes?
Make - up.
- I thought that was a girl move.
Looks he thinks.
- He won't have a girlfriend.
- I don't want a girl.
- Fag are you?
- Ove! That's not the expression.
- It wants to no matter where.
- Are you one of those gay people?
Yes. I am one of them.
I figured it out. What do you do are
you in a hurry?
Don't say anything about Mirsad. He
doesn't know his father.
I'm not one to gossip about others.
- You have a bigger problem.
- What?
It's like having a French car!
It might be good to know how the car
is moving.
It is not as simple as thought.
I have to pee.
- We can talk about the engine.
- I can't do. I'll be right back.
Hello. You're here already,
aren't you?
- The line is parked outside.
Lena Samuelsson, from the local
newspaper. Related to an accident at
the train station.
There's a man you saved his life.
- You're wrong, I'm not that person.
- I was there, I saw everything.
"Invisible heroes" we have a series
called.
I thought it would be appropriate for
you.
I'm sure there has been a lot of
excitement in your life.
- Are you talk about?
- No.
I have a letter from the man whose
life you saved. You should read it.
- Very touching. Wait...
- now I'm ready.
- We are not looking at now.
- Why? What was that?
- I've heard of a thing. Come on.
- Can you?
What? Locked or. An idiot could open
it even from the inside.
Idiots.
Ove!
Wait.
Did you think would disappear if you
closed the garage?
God...
You're stumped.
Ove...
- Nothing came to mind.
- That is bullshit.
Seriously. I can help you clean your
house.
- Put it in a ballast box or
something.
- You do not need.
- Sonja's things still hang.
- You do not need I said.
- Wouldn't it be nice if you
continued the path?
- I told you to stop talking!
I met Sonja, it was great, I'm sure.
But you brought him into some kind of
Saint.
Probably just wants to be Sonja.
But ordinary is great Sonja.
- Speech, I said!
- Keep your voice down!
All the idiots he keeps talking about
her...
Sonja is pushing the little memories
I have left from ...noise.
Sonja there was nothing before. After
that it won't be.
I'm for it.
Stop, you bastard! Wait, dammit, stop
it!
Hold on a second.
Adjourn this primitive attitude,
maybe we can make a deal.
- Off.
- Never. Go back, get lost.
We go by car if it's a problem at
City Hall you can call the manager
for you.
- You can help rune.
- I don't give a fuck Rune.
Here cars.
Even with a meter you can't go.
Really what is your problem, Ove?
In fact, I know. You're paranoid.
I did a little research on the
internet about you and from the
Municipal Archives.
I know everything.
Stupid letters that he sent to the
authorities.
I know everything about your wife and
the accident.
So he blames everyone and everything.
Or is this all your fault.
I'm going to complain.
I work for a private health care
company.
Decision-making we apply.
You should worry about your own
heart, you, Ove.
What do you know about my heart, Huh?
- What do you know about my heart?
- Sur.
Answer! What do you know about my
heart?
Stop the car! Stop that immediately!
Fucking idiot!
Fuck the white shirts! You know what!?
This is my final warning to you.
Leather tassels that will be tomorrow!
She's going crazy.
Forget it. Forget it, damn it.
No! Fight!
- Fucking-white shirts.
- Ove.
Ove, Hello? Unlock it!
Hello, Ove?
Are you okay?
- Ove! Come on, let it go.
- I'm not.
Yes.
Stop. First, close your eyes. Close
your eyes.
Here. Here. Stop!
- What is it?
- Come on, we'll dance.
No, no, no.  Yes, yes. Come
on.
I can't do.
We're home, you can handle it.
Ove. You're going to be a father.
We'll have kids!
I love you, Ove.
I love you too.
- Then we need to get a family car.
Yes, or it's a cradle.
It's a good idea. I'll make a cradle.
Damn bastards! What are you doing?
- We'd like to ask you something.
- What?!
Mirsad he was thrown out of the
House. Maybe you can keep it, he said.
Do you think that this hotel?
Mirsada revealed the secret.
I told my dad everything.
She hates those things.
It was one of her kids when she found
out she would have killed herself.
And just like that, anyway. We are
going.
Last always people to help.
Okay, come on.
Good Morning.
I made some toast. I made some coffee.
The site I'm going.
- Do you not drink coffee before?
I made a sandwich with some cheese.
Before you set up the site?
No, the first place I should check
out.
Can I come with you?
It's a free country.
All right, then.
Wait!
Hi. Can I come too?
I began to walk.
Hello. I'm Jimmy.  Hello.
Mirsad.
- Did you have a fight with your dad?
Yes.
He wasn't happy.
- Did you hear what happened rune?
- No.
They're going to come tomorrow.
They're taking you to a private
hospital.
It's bullshit. Until that happens
year by year.
Ask me, I know.
I swear to God. It was decided.
They're coming tomorrow.
An appeal his wife 3 years ago. But
now have to leave.
Three years. It's a lie. Sonja knew
them.
- , Too.
- Anita, Sonja would say something.
You didn't want to know.
- Why would she?
Asked for help.
Your problem is you can he said.
Said that?
I didn't need to know, he told me my
problem?
Yeah, what happened?
Idiot. I'm a complete idiot.
You shouldn't be mad at me, Sonja.
It's hard for people to accept their
own mistakes.
For a long time, especially when the
other person is incorrect.
I'm sorry.
But now it's time to do the right
thing.
When I fight how I know you're
worried.
But this time, you will agree with me.
Now it's time for war!
To me, municipal, and insurance
related to the church...
bring all your paperwork. I will help
you to Rune.
Press the star to terminate your
service.
Could I borrow your phone?
For the neighbours.
Does it matter what is being appealed
before!
Because there is a higher court.
Can't you read? Are you ignorant?
Blind ignorant! Hello?
Hello?!
How a person can just turn off the
phone, huh?
- Not for someone yelling at him?
- They're not listening to.
Sit down.
Turn it off.
It's always the same people.
It's the same people. As always.
Different names but same people.
The mayor of the place out of those
bastards.
Those damn white shirts.
Listen to his own words.
You said they never gave up, right?
Then sit down and feel sorry for
yourself.
Because you made the mistake of
making everyone look stupid.
Now you're giving up.
Because you think you can handle it
alone without help.
You know, Ove?
No one's alone I can't handle. No
one! So are you.
You can go now.
You can go I said. I'm exhausted for
you.
It was Sonja's idea completely.
We were going on a trip alone before
the child was born. And only then.
He insisted to go by bus.
It was more romantic, he said.
And I didn't object.
It was a little cheaper.
In southern Spain, the Romans did
what Sonja did.
As for me, about the Spanish
people and the buildings come to
Sweden...
...I am discovering that they need
to learn a lot.
We were having a great time.
We were eating outside in the
evenings.
Out for a nice dinner...
...from lunch we were separating
something.
Cheers.
Finally it was time to return home.
Hello.
Hello.  Thanks. You don't
need!
- Did what?
- Seems happy.
- Never Mind, Ove.
- What?
- That they're having fun.
- So what?
On the bus, he wanted to touch Sonja
stomach.
Because it was the baby kicking.
Look here.
- Do you feel?
- Is kicking all the time.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Sonja?
Sonja? Sonja?
Sonja!
Help! Help!
You can go in.
I think I sat next to a week.
One person even dared to talk to
me. It was for the best.
Until one day...
Sonja said You'd never wake up.
You can't tell me that!
Then an inexplicable thing
happened.
Had been the best and the worst
both at the same time.
The next day, I had to tell her
what happened.
About a life that doesn't exist
anymore.
Along with the pain I live in, I
felt a spiritual power.
First, I tried to spend my anger
on useful things.
Kept reading to the end.
Had a year to get his degree.
When school was over but couldn't
find a job.
A degree is really good, but I'm
sorry.
At that time, schools were not
suitable for disabled people.
One day, Sonja saw an ad in the
paper.
A class of merging all the
training techniques...
...both techniques revealed
before.
Your CV is really good but...
unfortunately, we can't afford
teachers with disabilities.
Then I was buried in darkness. I
wanted to destroy everyone.
Each a bastard. The driver is the
bus company...
...Vineyards, tour the company.
Everyone.
I wrote to both the Spanish
government and the Swedish
government...
...but nobody cared.
So people with disabilities can enter
will be flat.
Sonja's they haven't a ramp to
begin work.
I wrote a letter to everyone, I
know the reason I don't...
...for one thing, I was looking
for justice.
Until the last moment, Sonja
always was stronger.
Ove.
Either we live or die.
That night I did in one night what
you should go with the car.
The next day, could begin to run
after.
Welcome.
Homer wrote in the Iliad about the
Trojan War.
Well, when it was written The Iliad?
David?  - ? 700.
- BC.
- Come on.
Stenebo say hi to Richard. Welcome to
our class.
Hi, Richard!
- You're welcome.
I'm not lying. Within a year, the
same 400-year-old boy...
to quote from the poem ...the level
successfully graduated.
"Forever his craft"
"God, I think he's got his way"
"Creatures as an example for"
"Still for me... "
"... that is not from the land
beyond. "
Bravo!
Always fought for good things.
He never had for the child.
Died six months ago from cancer.
After I promised to go.
- Day today. Ready?
- Don't come any closer.
You've had three years to prepare for
this easily.
It was decided.
- It's for your own good, Anita.
- What about love?
The moment you separate us most that
we need each other my sake?
Are not even aware of where they are
24 hours a day.
True, but I am aware of.
And you take care of him, who
will?
- I'll look at.
- With a little help...
- a little help? From who?
Hello. Lena, from the local
newspaper.  Hello.
A shareholder from a health care
provider that you are special...
...some things I've heard. There is
talk of the unusual snow.
There is also a bank statement in the
Canary Islands.
Million about the deposit.
- Where did you find them?
- From the internet.
My editor loves this story...
but it's my decision, if you know
what I mean.
He had not returned.
Our time was better.
People was fighting for principles.
Ove! Ove!
Ove! Call an ambulance!
Don't stick the damn ambulance to the
site!
At the edge of the window.
Hello. Parvaneh, the highest in the
list you are.
Your father has a heart condition.
His heart is too big.
Sorry, Is it too big?  Yes.
But she'll be fine.
Ove!
You're too sick to die.
Damn it, I guess, the day came Ove!
Damn!
It was just collecting dust.
- Never been used.
- Very good, Ove. Thanks.
- You may need a little paint.
- Hold the baby.
Patrick, I'll show.
Hello, little one.
Get back down...
You are happy.
- There's something to you too.
- An iPad! Thanks, grandpa!
I know this feeling well.
Like when a new car.
This is the life.
Love the snow in front of the House
has been kuremem.
- Who cares.
- But eight hours.
The time to navigate the site.
Ove!
Don't think I did something
stupid.
If you're reading this, the
doctor's diagnosis was correct.
My heart was too big, he said.
Though it may seem like a nice
thing to it, not really.
Sooner or later pay the price.
I want a funeral in a church as it
should be.
Crap I don't want you swinging in
the wind like the Ashes.
I want to leave quietly,
considering I live right...
...accompanied by my relatives.
Place tuna the cat twice a day,
don't eat anything from the other
place.
Respect this!
And for God's sake, don't push the
cars to the site!
Translator: Achilles
Automatic Translation By:
www.elsubtitle.com
Visit Our Website For Free Translation